[{"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,1.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,2,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,3.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [3, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,4,4,4.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [4, 4, 4, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 1,4,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 4, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,1.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,3.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [3, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,2,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 1,4,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 4, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,2,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,2,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 2, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,4,4,4.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [4, 4, 4, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,3.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [3, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,3.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [3, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,1.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,2,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,2,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 2, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 1,4,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 4, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 1,3,4,1.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 4, 3, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 3,4,3,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 3, 4, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 4,1,4,2.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 4, 1, 4], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合-数一数/组合立体图形 数一数 2,3,2,1.svg", "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "3", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-06"}]